Mr. Rao and Mr. Patel are going to their
boss's retirement party
Bhaiya, how to go to Adarsh ​​Nagar Bhaiya,
take a left from the front
[Music] Go
straight and take the second right, then the first left,
from the circle we left right We came forward and then we came back
[Music]
Hey brother, it is late today also, I was not able to find the address
Sir, you should have used GPS
Retirement party is fine, but you have
used GPS in retirement planning, right, it is
late there too GPS in retirement planning
Presenting III Pru Gold Pension
Savings in which you get
savings for retirement, tax benefits and special cash
with draws III Pru Gold Pension
Savings for your retirement
[Music]
GPS